{
    "id": "46bcc339259a4ccaae8410d70ccc1f79",
    "title": "Combine the given sentences",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "0bfe5e5bd7564c6aa66836e289c536e6",
            "title": "Sentence Synthesis Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": ".................................... working very hard, he failed.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Despite",
                        "Though",
                        "However"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "........................................... you are honest, I will trust you.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "While",
                        "Since",
                        "That"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": ".............................................. the thief saw the policeman, he ran away.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "While",
                        "As soon as",
                        "No sooner"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is .................................................... to carry this box.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "enough strong",
                        "strong enough"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Iron ....................................... coal is found in India.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "also",
                        "as well",
                        "as well as"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is ..................................................... ill that the doctors do not expect him to recover.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "too",
                        "enough",
                        "so"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The boy ........................................... watch had been stolen complained to the teacher.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "whose",
                        "whom"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "................................................... on tip-toe, he reached for the apple.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Standing",
                        "Stood"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "This is the hotel ............................................. our meetings used to take place.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "where",
                        "there",
                        "here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Sudha is .......................................... intelligent to be defeated.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "too",
                        "so"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}